Hello everyone, I am Ivy from CLOUD, I am very happy to meet you again in the live broadcast room.
In fact, there is no face-to-face, we are in person.
There is also a mascot of CLOUD with me today, Finto.
He is a very cute little dog, Taiki.
Our live broadcast today is a bit special.
If we are friends in the mutual friend circle, you should be able to see that today's live broadcast is held at home.
Because the power outage and power outage in the office building today is really very difficult.
So I just made this live broadcast into a recording, and now it's at home.
And then in the course of our live broadcast today,
there may be the sound of this ding-dong, the sound of this Taiki dog.
I hope you don't mind.
So before I share with you the reconstruction of the building today,
let's talk to you about some of the problems left over from the last Q&A live broadcast.
The first question is how to fill in the slides.
This is actually a tool for graphics.
Let's open this project file first.
Let's load this file into CLOUD.
This is a project file that is done.
It doesn't have a broadcast on it.
We use this 2D or 3D in this sticker tool.
We click to find this PNG format sticker and directly add it in.
You can also click in the 2D or 3D version.
This version.
This version is added to this.
This sticker is added to this version.
Then how to fill it in?
We choose this PNG sticker tool.
Click on the right button.
Choose to repeat the version.
In this way, you can see that the whole PNG sticker is directly filled with this version.
We can copy and paste it to another version.
In this way, you can directly add it to another version.
Other versions also have the same principle.
We just copy and paste it and come over.
This is the first question.
The second question is about how to show reflective material.
We also open a file.
This is a skirt.
We first choose this shiny.
It is a little bit shiny.
Unlike matte.
And we can adjust the properties of this reflection.
The smaller it is, the brighter it is.
The stronger the reflection is, the brighter it is.
This is the overall brightness.
If we choose the properties of the default matte.
Still adjust the reflection properties.
Its reflection intensity and the roughness of the surface.
You can see that this is the overall brightness.
But in our normal process, we don't want the whole clothes to have this kind of brightening effect.
For example, like this pattern.
I hope it has the hard part.
It is not bright.
And the part without the hard part is bright.
At this time, we need to choose this high-light picture.
We put this high-light picture in.
The high-light picture is a black and white picture.
Its black part is reflected.
The white part is not reflected.
Let's load it in and have a look.
Let's pull it closer and have a look.
Let's add it again and have a look.
Have a look at its effect.
The black part is reflected.
The white part is not reflected.
Now you can see that after the load is in.
The white part of the flower is not reflected.
But the part without the flower is reflected.
Let's adjust its intensity.
You can see that the opposite means that it is reflected in the white part.
The black part is not reflected.
It is the opposite of the original high-light reflection principle.
Adjust its intensity.
Adjust its intensity and reflection intensity.
Let's take a look at its overall reflection effect.
This is the second question.
The third question is about how to show the gold and silver silk.
Let's talk about it here.
We still choose to open a file.
How to show the gold and silver silk?
In fact, it is very similar to the principle of pasting.
Use the principle of pasting.
Let's do it.
Let's add a sticker to show the effect of silver silk.
Let's put the file in first.
Then we use this sticker tool to find this PNG.
It's not going to be all white.
There are some white silk on it.
It's drawn in the PNG.
We also choose a version and add it.
Let's fill it up.
Then, in order to show its silver silk reflection,
we change its type to metal.
Then let's take a look at the rendering part.
This is the effect of gold and silver silk.
It looks like its surface reflection is very strong.
Because it is a metal attribute.
We choose this PNG sticker.
Let's make its transparency a little smaller.
And make its roughness a little bigger.
So that the reflection is not so strong.
Let's refresh it first.
Let's take a look at its effect.
This is the effect of silver silk.
We will continue to talk about the film later.
So let's not talk about it for now.
We will talk about it later.
The other problem is that
the position of the simulation picture is put behind the button,
and the simulation picture is not visible.
We have responded to the development.
If there is any improvement or update in other versions,
we will also tell you through the public number or live broadcast.
So it can't be solved at the moment.
There is another problem.
Many people say that there are many default fabrics at the window of the drawing room.
We add a piece of fabric to the window of the drawing room.
You can see that it has its own hair line cutout.
Some people say that in the default drawing,
I can't find the corresponding fabric.
The hair line cutout is blue.
It is difficult to distinguish.
There is no particularly good way to distinguish.
We can only distinguish by the name of the hair line cutout.
This is a better way.
Because it is in full English,
it may be a little difficult to identify.
If you change the Chinese when the fabric is changed,
we can also copy the path of the hair line cutout.
Let's go to the computer and find it.
Find its path.
This premise is that your fabric has also been changed to Chinese.
After we find its path,
we can also change the name of the corresponding hair line cutout to Chinese.
It's relatively simple to find it like this.
There it is.
Another way is to remove the hair line cutout of the hair line.
Then use the hair line cutout that is automatically generated.
This is the fastest way.
OK.
This is about how to distinguish the hair line cutout.
There are also people who ask about the knot.
If there is a knot,
I will give you an example today.
In the next live broadcast,
I will talk about how to make this knot.
Next,
we will start today's topic.
How to make trim.
First of all,
we will talk about the film.
How do we do it?
First, let's make a film in PS.
Let's open PS first.
Let's build a blank page.
Then let's add a new layer.
Let's use this oval selection box.
Press the Shift key to draw a positive circle for it.
Then we fill it in.
Fill in the color.
Because there is a little white in the middle of the metal.
There is a white place.
Look up.
So we fill in a gradient color.
There are many colors in it.
We can choose the film we want to make.
To fill in.
And we can adjust its color.
For example, the white in the middle.
Make it a little bigger.
Wait a minute.
I'm thirsty.
Click OK.
Then we fill it in directly.
After filling it in,
we choose to go back to this background again.
Let's choose this background.
Let's draw an oval in this background.
Because there is a gap in the middle of this beam.
Let's make a little gap in the middle.
After drawing the oval,
let's go back to this layer 1.
Delete the middle part of it.
Then we shrink the whole circle a little bit.
This circle is too big.
This beam is not that big.
Then we make a cut for it.
Turn off the background color.
It's a little flat.
Adjust it a little higher.
Then touch it.
Then cut it again.
This is equivalent to a double sequence.
Left and right.
Left and right sequence.
Let's save it again.
Save it as this PNG format.
Let's find the position first.
My name is because I have to use the obvious form to show the beam.
So I named it obvious.
This is one.
Then let's make a superimposed line.
That is, its obvious.
Superimposed beam.
Let's do the rules of its beam.
This is a lot of beam.
Then we close the layer.
Then do another cut.
Also make it a double sequence.
Left and right sequence.
Let's save it.
Because the save I press is the shortcut.
Ctrl Shift S.
Then I still save it as the PNG format.
Then we go back to the cloud.
Open a new project file.
OK.
Then we add this line.
We choose this line.
We put the type here.
We choose texture.
Then we change the texture.
We first choose the one we just made.
Single beam.
I often use some shortcut keys in the process.
If you don't understand.
You can ask in the background.
I don't know how to open it.
This is obvious.
Then we change its type to metal.
Then we go to the rendering interface.
Let's take a look.
This is a single beam.
Let's change another project file.
Let's make its internal line pattern.
Slightly drawn.
Drawing a little wave.
Then we put that.
The picture with multiple beam layers.
Add it directly in a linear way.
Still the same way.
Change the type to texture.
Then open its texture.
Let's zoom in a little bit.
Take a look.
There's a little bit of space here.
We can put its frame.
It's a little bit here.
A little bit of frame.
We'll turn it in the opposite direction.
Let's make it a little bit smaller.
Then here in addition to the texture.
We can change theíamoshaft.
Put it together.
That's how it's connected.
And then we look at the rendering interface.
Change it to metal.
Change the type to metal.
And refresh it.
And this is in the form of light.
To see it in a linear way.
This is a good rendering of this bright piece
You can take a look
The picture on the right is an enlarged picture
Next, let's talk about creating a self-defined button in the plugin
We cut to another interface
I opened two close interfaces
Because it's easier for us to do this
Let's draw a circle first
Let's make the diameter of the circle smaller
This is a single trim
Single copy
So the diameter of the circle, especially the circle
The smaller it is, the smoother the edge will be
If you like
If you have done this self-defined button
Everyone should know
We must put this button
Just put this board in the center of this cross
It can be self-defined into a button
Otherwise, the creation button will not succeed
We can take a look
After we simulated it, it did not touch the surface
So we will increase the thickness of the thickness
We can adjust the same contact surface
Then we missed the middle
The button missed the middle
We use the inner circle
We draw a stone
Then we convert the middle to a hole
Right-click convert to a hole
This is a button
Then we change its rendering thickness
Make it bigger
When it's too round
We can change its curve rate
The curve rate is changed to a little smaller
This is the curve rate
Its cold corner is more distinct
Then we add a texture to it
The dog just made a spray
I don't know if you can hear
OK
Then we just put it in the
We can export this file
You choose the file
Export
OBJ
Let's find a place to save
OK
Open a file
Let's look at how to do it
It is very simple
The first option we have to do is make a folder
We just have to do it
Because we want to do two
Let's do a nico1
Then here is all the versions
I just choose
Then is there a model here
There is no model here
So we can click to see the background
Select special file and copy
We have none here
Then one copy
One target and multiple targets
That one target is
and select multiple objects to create multiple targets.
The meaning of multiple targets here is that
the same fabric is applied to the same object
in the version you created,
so it doesn't matter if we choose one or more here.
We choose the thin and thick one below.
OK, choose the thin one.
You can see that the triangle has changed,
and then choose the single target.
You will find that this is the solution to the merger
and the gray light above the merger will show.
Removing the merger means that the points
where the plate is connected will be separated and poured out.
The merger is the point where the connection part of the
seam line in the plate is merged into one point and poured out.
In this case, we have no choice but to use one or more.
Here we choose the thick one.
We stick it in one point at a time and then we use it to connect the unit UV coordinates.
In order to guarantee that the UV image is not affected by any change,
there is no hidden object.
The following is the proportion,
and this is the axis transfer.
If there is a different axis in other software,
we can select this axis and change it.
The following file is to store the original logic path.
This is your sticker.
After you change the original path of the map,
you open this OBJ again.
It may lose the map,
so you can't change the original path.
The next one is to save it together with the text file.
Then it doesn't matter if your original text path will change.
It's a package anyway.
Just wait and find out.
The last one is to save this metal data.
Make a metal data.
We just choose to confirm here.
Then we enter the quick photo.
The purpose of the quick photo is that when we make our own buttons,
we want to put this button.
You have to distinguish which button you want,
so we will make a quick photo.
Let's open a project file again.
You can see that there is a
circle of this internal line.
We hope that the button will be added in this way.
Just add this button along this internal line.
First of all, we select the button in the physical window.
We are here.
There is a self-adjusted button here.
The number behind it.
Select the OBJ just now.
Then there is no preview image below.
It's stuck.
There is no preview image.
It's a button.
What kind of picture is the button?
This dog is a little hungry.
Our takeout is here.
We choose this one.
This is the picture of the fast train.
We click OK.
The button is successfully created.
Then we choose the tool to add the button.
Choose the button tool in the three steps.
We add it.
We add it this time along this line,
which is a little bit like a tree wheel line.
We adjust the size of the button from one side to the other.
We can increase the size of the button's original width.
A little bit smaller.
You can see that when the button in the three steps is adjusted,
the size of the button in the second step is also the same.
We adjust the size of the button once.
We add another button on the outside.
Now, we can sign in the device.
Then copy one out
Then apply it to the second increase on the button
Then make the width of its size a little bigger
It's so hungry
Copy again
Anyway, we just make it bigger once
Copy it to the second increase
This middle one has been used
We can delete it
Add to the second increase
This is the button
Change its type to metal
How it works
You can see that the reflection is very strong, you can't see it anymore, so we choose the button to change its type to plastic.
Let's take a look, this is plastic.
Let's take a look at the pictures of the metal material that we have calibrated.
Let's take a look at the inner line along this, this is the picture of the metal that has been calibrated.
From the inside to the outside, different sizes of buttons are added.
This is a method of adding buttons.
Let's go back to the interface that just made the button.
Let's put the middle space up again.
Let's make a little bit of a line on it.
Let's add a small rectangle on it.
Let's move it over.
Let this line go out a little bit longer.
Then adjust its diameter to be a little bit smaller.
Change its position in 3D.
Then let's delete its texture first.
Then let's change its edge curve.
OK.
Then we delete it to OBJ.
We name it as New Code 2.
We can just delete it according to the settings just now.
There is no need to change anything.
OK.
Then let's zoom in again.
Let's take a look at this new button.
OK.
Then we reopen a project file.
Let's change a way to add buttons.
We just added buttons in one way at a time.
Like this one.
For example, three rows.
It's also in the middle position.
When we do it, there are a lot of lines on it.
Do you see it?
It's like a small panel just now.
It's like a little line on the top.
In this way, we don't add buttons one by one.
Then how do we do it?
We are in the middle.
This is where we need to add.
We use the hook tool to hook it into a panel.
Hook it out first.
Then add buttons along the panel outline.
This is also a new function of 5.2.
I don't know if you have used it.
Let's apply a new fabric to it.
Let's apply a new fabric.
And then sew it together.
Remember to change its type of side sewing.
Sew again.
This is more basic.
Then we select other tabs other than this one that are new to us.
Refrige them.
To make it more simple.
Go with the back of the hook.
Let's add it to the outside
I see it's a little loose
Let's make it a little bit closer to the mirror
Make it a little tighter
Let's make the fabric a little harder
So it will be tighter
Then we cut the middle line and sew it
Because we want to add a button on all three lines
So we all have to cut and sew
Let's use this button tool
Let's give it a good addition
The same method is the same as the first one
First add this OBJ
Then add this shrink chart
Then this is the new button
Then we click on the outside of this board
Click on the right button
Let's add the button and buttonhole along the outside of the board
Then here
This one here
Let's make the diameter a little smaller
This number doesn't matter
Because I said it was 50
Why does it only appear 42?
Because it can only add 42 at most
So you can't count 50
Let's make it a little bit wider
Let me take a look
Let's make it a little bit thinner
Too thick
Then you can see this buttonhole to its edge
The edge is still a bit distant
We choose this buttonhole
Let's change the length of the line to 0
Let's make it a little bit closer
Then we use the same method to add other boards
Add this buttonhole on the outside line
This number is still the same
I said 50
It only appeared 39
That means it can only add 39 at most
It's useless to say 50
It's the same below
This dog has been running
It's hungry
Why is it so unsteady?
Because the object is the same
Let's write a new one
Just write the same value
0.25
And we're done
Ok then we come to copy
Different of this buttonhole
We make it different in size
And make it different in color
It's the same as what I just showed you
Let's change its width first
Then we change all of the types of it
Make this metal
Then change the second one to change the color a little
Change the third color
Did someone say that they couldn't hear my voice or something?
Anyway,
Let's pause this for a moment
And then make the sound a little louder
Let's talk about it
And then?
Let's change the transparency of the support version to zero
Because this version doesn't exist
We just gave it a bridge in the middle
Let's see the final effect through the rendering
OK
Let's look at this again
Let's look back
I just showed you this picture
And then we're going to make a ball for you
We delete this file
Or use this circle to make a ball
Make it a little smaller
Can be adjusted
Can not be adjusted
I chose not to change it here
And then?
But this is not a self-defined button to do OPJ
So do we want to move it to this one?
Move to this cross center
In fact, there is no need to emphasize that it is moved to this side
It doesn't matter if you move it or not
Anyway, make it an OBJ
It's not a self-defined button
Let's make it a little smaller
Because that pig is not that big
This is too big
Why did you draw a big one at the beginning?
It's because we want its edge to be more complete
It's more smooth
Not complete
Let's make it a big one after rendering
This circle is so big
Just like the earth
Can't say the earth
OK
Then we will export it
OBJ file export
OBJ
Then give it a name
Here we can put this
Because it doesn't have anything else
Because the coordinates are not the same
So we are now sure
OK
Then we go to this interface
Let's delete this version we just drew
Let's add the road again
Delete this inner line as well
Look at this one
I'm a little strong
See if I can't stand it
Then we open this road OBJ
Choose this rent
Go in
We must choose
Remember to choose to add the road as a secondary key
ah
Then we choose to stick it with this glue tool every day
Look at this too big
Who made it so big
I guess it's also rich and rich people
Anyway, I don't have one in my house
Okay, let's put it down
Then let's take a look
Let's change its material to this silk setting first
It's a pearl
Let's make a pearl
Reduce its reflection surface opacity a little bit
Make it brighter
ah
Let's take a look
Then this is the effect of the silk setting of this rent
Let's make it brighter on the wall
Let's refresh and take a look
Then we change it to this glitter powder
Let's take a look
Change a color
I don't know if you still remember
When we used to talk about glitter powder
That is to say
When we adjust this RGB
The value of the three-fold can't be too much
It's too much
He can't show it
Don't make it a little bit smaller
Just
Let's make this color a little bit less
A little bit more change in color
You can see this
The effect of this kind of glitter powder with five or six colors
Bling bling
ok
Then next
Let's change it to this metal metal effect
You'll find that there's a reflection in the back
There's a prominent place in the front
It's a little bit white
The color of the back is like this
ok
Then this is the effect of the rent
Let me show you
It's this one
Pearl
This glitter powder and this metal
And then we're going to give you a nail
Maybe you used to be doing nails
This kind of particularly hard one
This kind of add-on
We're all in other 3D files
For example, 3D Max
Other 3D files do
Then we share today
How to do it in Closet
I'll draw a circle at the bottom first
You see
Let's adjust it to the internal line
Fold two
One is as the middle of this nail
The middle of the scale
There's also a piece of the top of the ring on the link
A piece of it
I might have said that you didn't have a floating line in your mind.
I'm sorry
People might not understand
And may not react
Let's take a look
I'll drink water first
I justid quickly
This board was whilst corrected
I press the shortcut
Ctrl C
Then we put it in this board
The purpose is to wait for us to do this
When redrawing 3D arrangement
The 3 of them are together
It's more convenient
And then we move it
This dog is a little weak
Let's put it in its place
What about this
In fact, because I made a copy
Then he actually can't do it
Do you want to take it as this
Put it in the center of the cross
In fact, there is no difference
You can put it in or not
But when you do the self-locking
You must put it in the center of the cross
To be able to self-lock
Then we put the top two small ones
First grind it up
Revive it
Then we grind the bottom plate
You can see that it still has no contact
Let's change its speed to zero
Let it contact
Then change its one
Let's delete this internal line first
It's still hanging
It's hungry
Then make the back of the top a little bigger
Make the bend a little smaller
Then put the narrow one in the middle
Put it on too
Then make the back of the back of the back a little bigger
Then change the bend rate to 20
Let's make the back of the back of the back of the back of the plate
Make it a little bigger
It's the same
Then this is the top part
The top part
Let's press it down first
Then wait a minute
Its function is to sew that plate
That's the cylinder
Did you see it just now
Its length
That's the length of the line just now
It should be more than 125
That 125
Then let's take a look at the cylinder we're going to draw
How much is its radius
It's actually about the length of an equilateral triangle
It's actually the length of the triangle divided by the number two
And then it's about 89
And then?
Because its diagonal is not a straight line
We're going to wait for the equilateral triangle
Its diagonal should be a straight line
We don't have a straight line
It's a curve
So we can appropriately change its radius to 89
To make it a little smaller
That is to say
We can change it to 80
We can adjust it
Let's try it
Take a look
Let's draw a radius
The width is 80
The length of the border is 80
This curve
And then?
We use this
This is the tool for creating a round curve
Turn its edge into a curve
So we can take a look at this length
You can see it's 129
Just when you see it
In fact, it's four millimeters away
Okay, let's make it a little smaller
And then we're at the top of it
Give it a touch
Wait a minute
We'll add a fixed needle to it at the top
Add a needle
And then we're going to sew it
Well, let's take a look at this direction of determination
Now the blue dot is to determine the direction for it
Okay, and then I'll show you the direction
Okay, and then we'll give it a little simulation
The one on the bottom
Give it to him
Oh, I can't do it
I'm going to freeze the bottom first
I can't do it again
Yeah, there's no seam on this side
Let's sew it again
You can see that we're going to change the shape of this line
Why?
Because you can look at it again
It's going to come out and come out
It's not as round as it was just now
It's not as round as it was in the seam
Let's adjust the shape of this curve
You can see that the one just now is a little bit to the side
It's a little bit to the side on the side
Let's adjust it a little bit
It's much better this way
Let's move it a little bit
Then let's put it in and make it a little bit smaller
Change to one and model it again
Let's add a piece of this fabric
Let's change it
Make it harder
Then let's model it again
Let's change the bottom again
Harden it a little bit
It seems to be very conflicted
After hardening, we'll really put the fabric on it
Let's take a look
This is the back
It's a little bit out
Let's turn it over
Let's model it again
It's much better
It's much better now
When you're doing it
If you have this situation
We also want to take a look at this
The difference between the texture surface and the texture surface
Let me print this fabric
Let's model it again
Relatively speaking, it's very hard to do this way
It's very hard to do this way
It's much harder
We put this on the side
The hairpin sticker
The hairpin sticker on the side
The strength of the sticker is turned off
Let it look like a round
At least it looks like that
Otherwise, there is a gap in the middle
What's going on
Ok, then we turn it over to obj
As you can see
We just put this in here
We directly choose the default one
You can just select the default one, not the single one, but the multiple one.
As you can see, we just used two pieces of fabric.
When we wait for it to be used, I also said that the multiple target is to use the same piece of fabric as a target.
So when we import it into the plugin, let's see if it should have two targets.
One is the top ring and the other is the bottom plate.
Let's pinch it.
This nail is a bit big.
Don't mind it.
Let's touch it.
Let's make it a little bit smaller.
Let's take a look.
It's two now.
The multiple targets we just said are corresponding.
Make it a little bit smaller.
Let's pinch it again.
OK.
Then we can copy one out.
Let's select this copy key.
We directly select Ctrl C, Ctrl V.
It's faster.
OK.
Then I'll make this flipped.
I'll make it a little bit smaller.
Let's pull it out first.
OK, let's select these two nail targets.
We can select one of them.
Then right-click and select all of the copy keys.
Then change its type to Netl.
Then we can also add a lot of molding below
I won't show it here
I'll show you this added and fermented bone
This is the effect of molding
It was so good when it was made
This is the molding
Then let's talk about the 8-word buckle of this strap
We have a lot of customers doing this bra recently
Let's take a look at the 8-word buckle
Let's draw a curve first
Then we turn it into a circle
Because the 4 corners of the 8-word buckle are not so sharp
It's not this
It's not really a curve
Let's make it a little bit round
OK
Then we make it smaller with the example
Then we make it a inner line
The inner line is a border
Then let it be hollow
This is the adjustment buckle
We have to wear the belt in the middle
Then we opened it
This is an adjustment buckle
You can see its width
The width above is 37.5
Let's draw one for him
I also drew 37.5 here
Actually, it's not necessarily
If there is a tie tie
If it's narrow
You can draw it a little smaller
I'm here to draw it according to its width
Because he is involved in this cross-sectional video
I mean, it's under the ground, and then I'll add a different fabric to it
And then we're going to freeze this eight-point buckle and then we're going to put this strap on and we're going to put it on and we're going to make it a little smaller
And then we're going to add a little bit to this
I'm going to add a pattern to this strap
Why did I choose this pattern here because when I was waiting for the demonstration it was related to this pattern so you can do this
This buckle is the eight-point buckle this file as a project file to preserve the following pattern is convenient for us to cover convenient for us to use
It's not hard for you to have any pattern and then we're going to put this eight-point buckle on and we're going to make it a little bigger
The color of the pattern is washed away
The main reason is that we want to do it when we do it and it's a little bit more convenient when we change the color of the same pattern because everyone knows that this
The red one would have been very inconvenient if I had changed the color
So we'll just pick this one and we'll pick this one and we'll pick the one that's going to keep the file holdin g together and we'll pick the one that's going to compress the bag
In other words, your physical path has changed your relationship
Let's open this thing
I often use some shortcut keys here
This will save time
So sometimes you may see that my operation is very fast
Just click on the shortcut key
Let's import this zip directly
Add and import as a copy
Then let's take a look at this copy
The text we just added
Is the same as the text we just added
Let's make it smaller
It's too big
Make it smaller
Make it a little bit bigger
Make it a little bit smaller
Then we can adjust the color of the belt
To match the volume
This will connect the belt
And then I will change the type of 8-digit buckle
To metal
OK
As you can see
The buckle is a little bit
Just hide the buckle
OK
Then the last part
Let me tell you
How to make this
Pairing
Let's draw a zippered copy first
Can draw anything
I'm a little hesitant
Then we can
This copy you need to draw
As an editor or jpg, you can just type it in as a sticker.
Let's make it bigger.
This picture is too big, more than 2000.
Let's make it a little smaller.
This is the date code we need to draw today.
But you don't have to do this.
Anyway, all the components you want to make are made in this way.
Then we adjust the shape we just drew.
Let it make a date code like this.
I chose this one.
It's easier to do.
Why?
Because it's four points.
How do you say that?
We can see that it's actually a left and right symmetry.
Up and down symmetry.
So when I'm doing it, I'm going to make it a part of it.
In other words, I just need to make it one-fourth of it.
I can use other methods to expand it.
Just expand it.
You don't have to draw it one by one like this.
But if you don't follow the rules, you'll have to draw it one by one.
Let's adjust it a little bit.
You don't have to do the same.
Because we can make this sticker a little bit bigger.
Or make it smaller.
Let it adapt to the shape we drew.
Draw this board.
I just said that we just need to make it one-fourth of it.
Let's add a line in the middle.
Add a dot.
Then we draw a segment line for it.
Then we draw it left and right.
Then we choose this line.
Click the right button.
Choose to cut.
Then I cut this board.
It's not at the top.
Then we choose this line.
Give it a straight line.
I'll cut it again.
We delete this.
Then delete the part below this.
We leave it one-fourth is enough.
Then we are inside.
You see, there is a hollow part inside.
Now there is no hollow inside.
Let's make the example a little smaller.
Let its circle look natural.
Let's draw it inside.
Let's use the inner line.
The shortcut key is G.
This method, press the control key.
You can draw it on this side.
Press the control key.
You can draw a curve line.
Let me adjust this part a little.
Let's adjust the angle of the corner
OK
Then we can open it
Let's open it up and down
Then we put this inner line
You will find that there is an empty point in the middle of the inner line
The point is broken
Adjust the bottom first
Adjust it a little bit
Pull down a little
Wait a minute
Let's deal with the empty point above
Because we are going to be hollowed out for a while
The empty point must not be hollowed out
It's not a closed shape
So we wait
I'm sure I'm going to put these empty spots
Let's put it together first
Both sides are the same
Some people say that the time is too short
I can't hear enough
If you can't hear enough
Then you can only watch the live broadcast
Or you can only watch the live broadcast
Then we choose the middle line
Empty
Well, now you can see the back of it
It is still this white
Then we can turn it from the side
We can make it yellow
Make it yellow all the way
Make the front yellow
Then we turn it to OBJ
While you are watching, look at the screen
I'm going to zoom in a little bit
to the front
Light on the edge
Light on the front
OK
Here we choose the default value
We want to keep the text and file together
This can ensure that your text is in the original path
There will be no errors in the transmission process
Some people may not be able to receive your text
Can't see it, it's white
Let's import it
Import this日子扣
Here we import it as a copy
Let's take a look at the bottom
There is a little bit
It's okay, let's make it a little bit smaller
This is all the training we're going to talk about today
How to make
And now
I want to see if you have any questions
Can ask
Today's conditions are a bit difficult
If there are some questions that can't be answered today
We will also be in the next live broadcast
Pick some of the questions you ask
Tell you
Today C is very excited
Because we changed a
We changed a live broadcast room
So he wants to tell you guys
Let's make a few words
Let's let him tell you guys
I'm walking now
Let him make a seat
Let me take a look at your questions
Hello everyone
I am the limited voice today
Can you hear my voice now?
Can you recognize who I am now?
No one knows
So embarrassing
I'm your cute teacher Molly
I accompanied you for nine lessons
No one recognized me
I'm so sad
I just saw a question
That is
Someone asked
Can these parts be included in the simulation?
Yes
Didn't I use it just now?
Water supply
It's stuck
How do you move your clothes?
How does he move
Not last week live broadcast
I played the teacher on last week stream
The teacher of the live stream last week is
Mr. Usia
I gave you a whole series of basic lessons
And someone else mentioned the machine
I'm so sad
Why do people mention machines every time I come out
Yes yes
Is Mr. Molly
Yes, your live class goddess
He said, the beautiful face of Molly
Thank you
I see that everyone has any questions to ask
Someone said that he won't do that circle
Which circle won't do
That ball
Won't that ball do it?
I will show you how to make this ball on the spot
This ball is actually very simple
Let's use this round tool first
Let's draw a radius of 50 here
This is a circle like this
Then we can see that the edge of it is not
Isn't this cold corner more distinct?
Then we change its particle diameter to a little smaller
For example, let's change it to 1
Then click yes
Then of course this circle
If we adjust its rendering speed to 100
It will be very big
First of all
Let's make its size feel a little smaller
When we shrink it
We can use its corner
Press and hold the left key
Select its corner and shrink it
Then press the Shift key
Then the left key does not loosen
Shift key does not loosen
Single right key
If you have participated in training
You should know that there are often many keys in the code
Left key, right key, Shift key, Control key
It may be a little dizzy at first
But it's okay if you're used to it
Let's set its width to 4
Click to confirm
Then we set its rendering thickness to 100
You can see that it is now a very large sphere
Right
This ball doesn't matter
Just put it aside
Just put it in this
Then we select the file
Exit as obj is ok
Exit as obj
Save it
We choose
Because it's just a card
So you choose single goal or multiple goals
Actually no difference
But you must choose a thick one
We chose thin
We choose to confirm
Then we in another file
We choose the file
Exit as obj
Here you must remember
You need to choose
Then this increase is entered as a negative key
Ah must be entered as a negative key
Choose to confirm
I don't know what the math formula is
Ah math formula
I'll finish this first
Put this on first
That's how it's stuck
Let's make it a little smaller
Let's change it to 10 here
Just one small one
Okay, this is the circle
The math formula is like this
Because when we are doing the circle
Then you must make one of these
The right-angled triangle on the left side to draw it, right?
But change it to a circle on the left side
And then the circle we just drew
For example, if we draw a circle casually
Draw a circle casually
For example, 50
Then you
Isn't its axis this
The length of the line on its left is the same as the length of the line on the right
So you can draw a circle
The length of the line we just drew was 125
Now it's 156.9
You take it and divide it by the root number 2
The root number 2 is not its one
The triangle of the right-angled triangle on the left side
And then but we
It's not round on its right-hand side
Its right-hand side is not a straight line
It's a curve
So we can take it and divide it by the root number 2
Make it a little smaller
I just I was at that time
Uh, I tried it
It should be about 89 when it started to calculate
But let's make it a little bit
Let's make it a little bit smaller
It doesn't matter if you don't know this
You just try it one by one
For example, this is 156
You divide by the root number
About 1.4
It's actually 10
It's just 100
You don't want 100
You just set 80 or 90
It should be 90 here
It's almost 90
Maybe because I'm an engineering girl
PCB
Ah, don't be shy
Don't be Mrs.
Uh
Not số
It's not bad
Well that's not wrong
It doesn't matter when you are using cloud
When you are using this, you just try it
Anyway, you can do it by dividing its length by 2π
Can be 2π 6.2 6.28
The next topic is
Isn't it the top of Fujian's production today?
The next time is the next level of Fujian's production
There will be a self-taught big card of cloud
To tell you more about the content
Don't miss it at that time
The next time to talk about Trim's high street
Today is the middle and low street
Steel ring mold cup
It needs to be made by yourself
Need to make it yourself
Need to
Good good
Looking forward to the high street
What kind of bulldozer are you talking about?
Is it a robbery?
There will be a low after
There are two minutes left
There are two minutes left to make a mistake
We're going to eat
I'm going to eat
This one wants to eat
The stars are very hungry
He has stepped on me several times
9 o'clock is not a on-time line
I see if everyone has any problems
If there are many problems
We can solve them again
Then here is the first time in advance
Wish everyone a good day
I wish you a happy holiday!
Can I see the auspicious object?
Let's do it next time, okay?
She's very good today, she's very hungry, she's already lying on the bed.
Ling Yi, socks.
Thank you, you're welcome.
May I ask if you're my client?
You're in my circle of friends.
I'm indeed in your circle of friends right now.
You're in my circle of friends right now.
Teacher Tina is not here right now.
And then, she'll be in charge of the next high street train.
If you want to come to Shanghai to work, come quickly.
Shanghai is very welcoming.
If there are no more questions, we'll end the live stream today.
Once again, I wish you all a happy Chinese New Year.
Happy Chinese New Year!
Bye bye!